캘리포니아 타자나 1992
-일어나!
-난 그냥 누워 있는게 좋은데.
Get up!
- I'm actually good down here.
철들어 모건 그라임스!
Grow up,
Morgan Grimes!
체육관에서 계속 훔쳐보더라
You were spying on me
in gym class.
박살내...
I'm going to kick your...
살려줘!
Help!
걱정마 모건
내가 도와줄게
Don't worry, Morgan.
I got your back.
수지
Suzy,
내가 잘 얘기해 볼게
I'll take it from here.
모건, 넌 아마
Morgan, maybe
한동안 여자에게서
피해 있어야겠다
you should stay away
from girls, for, like,
한 15년 쯤?
15 years?
15년 뒤
좋아 이거봐
All right,
check it out.
네 전 여자친구 사진?
A picture
of your ex-girlfriend?
그게....내 금쪽같은
That.. that's why I had
휴식시간에 여기로 불려온 이유야?
to come in here
on my coffee break?
애나 멜린다 우
Anna Melinda Wu.
158cm, 48kg,
의 중국계 소녀지
Five - two, 96 pounds,
of Chinese descent.
왜, 왜 우리가 여기서 네
전 여자친구에 대해 얘기하고 있는거지?
Why-why... why are we in here
talking about your ex?
왜냐하면 오늘
Because today,
너희들이 도와주어야 할
I need your help
임무가 있거든
on a mission.
무슨 미션?
What kind of mission?
-스파이 미션이지, 찰스
-감당할 수 있겠어?
A spy mission, Charles.
- Can you handle it?
있지, 난 말야
You see, I'm afraid
안나가 새 남자를
만나는 것 같아 기분이 좋지 않아
Anna may be seeing a new guy.
워!워! 잠깐만
Whoa! Whoa!
Hey, time out.
나보고 안나를 염탐하라구?
You want me to spy on Anna?
물론 아니지 넌 우리가
너무 과하지 않는가만 살펴주면 돼
Course not, Chuck. You'd be
there for moral support.
넌 염탐 기술이 부족해
You're not skilled in
spy-craft. No, that's where
그래서 레스터와 제프가 맡아줄거야
Lester and
Jeff come in.
나랑 만났던 여자의 80%는
Does it shock you
아무 생각없었다니
that 80%
of my encounters with women
놀랍지 않아?
have been completely
without their knowledge?
솔직히 나머지 20%가 더 신경쓰여
Honestly, I'm more surprised
by the other 20%, Jeff.
이봐 친구 니가 요즘에
힘든 시기를 보낸걸 잘 알아
Look, buddy, I know you're going
through a tough time,
그렇지만 난 다른 누군가를
but I just don't
feel comfortable stalking
스토킹하는건 좀 아닌것 같아
another human being.
이봐, 이건 스토킹이 아냐, 알겠어?
Dude, it's not stalking, okay?
이건 다른 이를 신경쓰지만, 그 사람에 대해
It's caring enough about someone
to learn things about them
알 수 없을 때 스스로 할 수 있는 방법이야
they won't tell
you themselves.
그게 스토킹이지
Which is stalking.
그리고 난 니가 꼭 필요해
And I really need
you on this one,
그러니까....
so...
제발, 데본, 당신 도움이 필요해
Please, Devon,
I really need you.
일하러 다시 가려면 몇 분밖에 안남았지만
Only got a couple minutes
before I got to get to work,
당신이 신경쓰지 않는다면야
but if you don't mind
a little drive-thru
후다닥 해치울 수도 있....
when you're used
to fine dining...
아냐, 아냐, 아냐, 아냐,
No. No, no, no.
그게 아니라 당신 도움이 필요해서 그래
No. Not-not for that.
I just... I need your help.
이건 우리 결혼식까지
해야할일 리스트야
This is our to-do
list for our wedding.
-지루하겠네
-이 일들을 나혼자
Ooh. Less fun.
- There's just not enough hours
다 처리해 버리기엔 시간이 부족해
in the day for me
to do everything myself,
야간 근무도 해야하고
누나 노릇도 해야 하고
plus work night shifts,
and plus be a sister
친구노릇도, 여자친구노릇도....
and a friend and a girlfriend...
약혼자노릇이지
Fianc?.
그러니깐 내 말은 당신이
My point is, is that I need you
내 짐을 좀 덜어줬으면 좋겠어,
할 수 있지?
to start pulling your weight
around here, okay?
그러니깐 당신은 꽃이랑
So you can deal
with the flowers,
음악과 케이크를 맡아 줬으면 해
the music and the cake.
내가 나머지를 처리할 게
I will handle the rest.
자기야 자기야
Babe. Babe.
결혼이 파트너쉽이 필요하다면
A marriage is
a partnership.
결혼식도 마찬가지여야 해
A wedding
should be, too.
알았어
Okay.
워! 이건 다 뭐하는거야?
Whoa! What is this place?
우리 친구 제프리가 단지 마시고 먹고하는데만
Whatever our friend Jeffery here
doesn't guzzle down his throat,
돈을 쓰지 않았다는 증거지
He spends on spy gear.
놀랍지, 그렇지?
Incredible, right?
놀라울정도로 지저분하네
Incredibly creepy.
이봐, 숙녀분들 가자구
Hey, ladies, let's go.
각자 자리로 돌아가
Man your posts.
이렇게 벌건 대낮부터
Babysitting the freak show.
저게 대체 뭐하는 짓거리야
This should be enlightening.
아, 대상이 시야에 들어왔다
Ah, we have visual acquisition
of the target.
도청준비 완료
We got ears on.
대상이 이동한다
Subject is on the move.
이봐, 이봐 이러면 안돼
Guys. Guys,
we can't do this.
지금 당장 그만둬야해
We shouldn't be doing this
right now.
무슨, 미친 스토커 같자나
I mean, we're,
like crazy stalkers.
쉬!찰스 좀...!
Shh! Charles, please!
저것들이 미쳐서
What the hell are these crazy
저런 스토커 짓을 하는거야?
stalkers up to?
웬만한 스파이들 저리가라할 정도네요
Looks like some
pretty decent spy work.
우리 잠깐만 그만두고
Would you just stop
and think
우리가 무슨짓을 하는지 생각해볼래?
about what you're doing
for a second?
척, 나도 지금 내가
무슨일을 하는지 잘 알고 있어, 형제
Chuck, I know exactly
what I'm doing, brother.
나도 답을 알아가고 있다구
I'm getting answers, man.
그래, 그래도 다른 방법으로
얻을수도 있지 않을까?
Yeah, but there are other ways
of doing that.
아니 절대로 다른 방법은 없어
Yeah. No. Absolutely.
안나의 휴대전화를 복제하려 해봤는데
그 전화가 코드분할다중접속 방식이라
We tried cloning Anna's cell,
but she's got a CDMA carrier,
우리가 USIM칩을 얻지 못했어
so we couldn't
copy the SIM card.
잠깐, 잠깐, 잠깐, 잠깐,
잠깐, 잠깐, 저기 저 남자다
Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait. Here. There's a guy.
지금 나타난 저 남자야
There's a guy
just showed up.
나도 보자
나도 봐
Quick. Let me see.
Let me see.
우
Ooh.
아마 그녀의 오빠일거야
Maybe it's her brother.
오
Oh.
그래도
Still,
그녀 오빠일수 있자나
could be her brother.
좋아
All right.
돌아가자
미션 중지야
Let's back it up.
Abort mission.
난 저 녀석이랑 게임이 되질 않아,척
I mean, I can't compete
with this guy, Chuck.
건강한 머릿결에
He's got healthy hair,
환한 미소, 그리고
죽이는 차도 있자나
a clean smile
and a killer car.
보라구
Look at him.
그니까
I mean,
상상 이상으로 최악이야...
he's my worst nightmare!
그래 니 예감이 맞을거 같다, 친구
Yeah. I'd trust
your instincts, pal.
장관님께서 조금뒤에
Uh, the general
will be available
제이슨 왕에 대해
이야기하기 위해 접속하실거에요
to talk about the Jason Wang
situation momentarily.
저기, 근데 여기 있는건
왜 갖고 있는거에요?
Hey, how come you guys
have these in here anyway?
가끔 치나 보죠?
I mean, do you play?
진짜 공이 아니에요
They're not toys, Chuck.
뚜껑부분을 한번 누르면
If you pop the top, they are
쇠도 녹일수 있는 백린탄이 되요
white phosphorous grenades.
They can melt iron.
알겠슴다
Okeydokey.
그럼 이건 미니 화염방사기 인가요?
What are these,
mini flamethrowers?
민트향의 기절 스프레이야
Uh. Mint-flavored
knockout spray.
아! 진짜요? 제가 하나 챙겨도 될까요?
Oh! Really? Do you think
I can have one of these?
제가 아시다시피 여기저기서
많이 공격받는 타입이라서요
'Cause I'm always, you know,
really vulnerable out there.
제이슨 왕
안나 우의 새 남자친구
Jason Wang,
Anna Wu's new boyfriend.
왕은 차량 수입업자라네
Wang's a car importer,
삼합회의 위험한
동료들로부터 도망친 후
and while
he has no criminal record,
한동안은 아무 전과도 없이
조용히 지내고 있었지
he runs with a dangerous crew
of local Triad gangsters.
이 녀석들은 LA외곽지역에서 총기나 마약
A gang responsible
for smuggling guns, drugs
다른 무기류들을 모으고 있었습니다
and other weapons in
and out of Los Angeles.
그렇다네 워커 요원
Correct, Agent Walker.
우리는 지역내의
삼합회일당을 주시하고 있었네
We've been watching
the local Triad for a while,
하지만 척이 뭔가를 알아내기 전까진
but didn't know
about Wang's involvement
왕이 연루되어 있는줄은 몰랐다네
before Chuck's flash.
천만에요
Well, you're welcome.
저한테 고맙지 않으면
You really don't have
to thank me.
고맙다고 하시지 않아도 되요
Not-not that
you are thanking me.
지금 얘기 하시는 것에
I guess you're
really just kind of
더 집중하고 싶으신 거군요
making a statement. Continue.
자네들의 임무는 왕과 삼합회의
Your mission is
to determine the depth
관계를 파해 치는 거라네
of Wang's connection to Triad.
척, 침투하면서 의심을 받지 않도록
Chuck, use
your social connection
자네의 대인 관계를 이용하게
to infiltrate the suspect.
잠시만요 장관님
Um, excuse me, General,
그러니깐 확실히 말하자면 제가
but just-just to
clarify-- you want me
제 제일 친한 친구의 전 여자친구의
새 남자친구와 친구가 되라는 말이에요?
to befriend my best friend's
ex-girlfriend's new boyfriend?
무슨 문제 있나
바토스키 군?
Is there a problem,
Mr. Bartowski?
아뇨, 아닙니다
No. Nope.
무,,문...문..문제가 아니죠
No. Not a... Not a problem.
엄청 큰 문제 이지요
I got a big problem here.
DC 기미갤 킁이 제작
수정 배포 자유
영자막 제공 ★그림자
DC 기미갤 킁이 제작
수정 배포 자유
영자막 제공 ★그림자
# na-na na-na na-na #
Chuck S02 E14
Chuck VS The Best Friend
# na-na na-na
na-na #
피드백 directman@nate.com
# na-na na-na na-na #
# na-na na-na
na-na #
언제나 훈훈한 기미갤로 놀러오세요
# na-na na-na na-na #
환절기에 감기 조심
# na-na na-na
na-na. #
잘잤어 척?
Sleep well last night, Chuck?
뭐야?
What?
아니 실은 어젯밤에
Actually, no.
I was having
사람들이 날 스파이하는 악몽을 꿨어
nightmares about
people spying on me,
그니까,..그게 너무
생생했다는 말이지
Which-which... which
now feels all too real.
내가 할 말은
My point was
니가 자고 있는 동안
that while
you were still here asleep,
난 일하다가 지금에서야
들어왔다는 거지
I'm just now
getting home from work.
힘든 날이었지
생명을 구하는건
Tough night.
Saving lives
꽤나 멋진 일이지
can get pretty gnarly sometimes.
내 말이
Tell me about it.
그래서 오늘 무슨 계획이야?
So, what are your plans
for today?
음, 너도 알다시피 일하러 가겠지 우선
Uh, well, you know, I mean,
I-I probably have to go to work.
알자나, 그리고
You know?
- Mm.
그후에 사라랑 피자나 먹고
노닥거리겠지 뭐
And, uh, I-I might get a
pizza with Sarah afterwards
아님 뭐 다른걸 하든가, 알면서
or something, you know?
달콤한 생활이네,그치?
Cakewalk, huh?
네 달콤한 삶을 누리기 전에 말야
Considering your mellow skedge,
곧 네 매형이 될
나의 부탁을 좀 들어주지 않겠어?
what do you say, you help out
your soon-to-be brother-in-law?
무슨 일인데?
What'd you have in mind?
엘리는 내가 결혼식때
부를 밴드를 정하기를 원해
Ellie wants me to find a band
for the wedding,
그리고 난 네가 얼마나
음악을 좋아하는지 알고 있었지
and I know how much
you love music,
그리고 내가 얼마나 바쁜지도
and how busy I am.
그래서 내 생각에 이건 정말
윈-윈 전략일 거라는 생각이 든거야
So, I was thinking, this
could be a win-win situation
우리 둘에게 말이야
for both of us.
나보고 밴드를 정하라구?
You want me to find a
band for your wedding?
잘 됐구나, 척
That'd be awesome, dude.
고마워
Thanks a lot.
난 할 수 없어요
I can't do this.
어떻게 장관님이 제게
이런 일을 시킬수 있죠?
How can the General ask me
to do this?
그 여자는 무슨 날때부터
마빡에 별이라도 달고 나왔대요?
I mean, was the woman born
with stars on her shoulders?
친구도 하나도 없었나보죠?
Has she never had a friend
before?
내 친한 친구의 전 여자친구의 새 남자친구와
I can't just go and hang out
희희낙락 하기엔
with my best friend's ex
and her new boyfriend
이건 너무 큰 문제 에요
like it's no big deal!
당신이 모건을 대하는걸 보면
I understand
that this may be difficult
이게 얼마나 어려운 일인지
저도 잘 알아요
for you with regard to Morgan...
아니, 아니, 아니, 아니,
아니죠, 어려운게 아니라
No. No, no, no, no.
No, not difficult.
일어날수 없는 일이에요!
Not happening!
모건은 유치원에 다닐때부터
제 제일 친한 친구였어요
Morgan has been my best
friend since kindergarten.
모건이 이 사실을 알면
무슨 짓을 할지 상상도 할 수 없어요
I don't even know what
he would do if he found out.
미안해요, 척 그렇지만
이건 선택할 수 없는 문제에요
I'm sorry, Chuck,
but this is not an optional.
직접 내려진 명령이에요
It's a direct order.
내 제일 친한 친구를
그렇게 배신할 수 없어요
I can't betray
my best friend!
아무도 이해 못하는거에요?
How come nobody gets that?!
흠,'충성'이지(Semper Fidelis)
Hmm. Semper Fidelis.
이 말은 해병대에서 쓰는
"언제나 믿고 있어라"라는 말이지
It means, "always faithful"
in the Marines.
민간인 입장에서 보면
In civilian life, it means
네 자신 보다, 네 친구를
생각하는 그런 마음이겠지,응?
putting your friend's well-being
above your own, huh?
네게 경의를 표하지
바토스키
I salute you for that,
Bartowski.
잘 했어
Well done.
그래요, 그거
Yeah. That's...
고마워요 케이시
충성이죠, 충성(Semper Fi)
Thanks, Casey. Yeah,
Semper Fi. Semper Fi.
여기 이 케이시가 이렇게 감정을
You know, it's a pretty upside
down world when this guy's
감정을 내비치다니 놀랍네요
the one picking up on the
emotional nuances around here.
좋아요, 그럼 장관님께
말씀드리러 가요
All right,
let's go tell the General.
그래, 그렇지만 내가
네게 경의를 표하는 다른이유는
Yeah, but as much as I
respect your Code of Honor,
나는 도저히
할수 없는 일이기 때문이지
there's nothing
I can do about it.
이번 만큼은 명예보단,
명령에 따라줘 바토스키
Orders before honor
this time, Bartowski.
안나의 새 남자친구의 친구가 되어줘
Go befriend Anna's
new boyfriend.
그럼, 음, 당신은
So, um, how would you...
누구 음악을 제일 많이 듣고 자랐나요?
How would you categorize
your music?
그러니깐, 누가 당신에게
I me, who-who are kind of
가장 큰 영향을 미쳤나요?
your more major influences?
예,
Uh-huh.
저기요 전 맥스 삼촌의 유대 음악 밴드가
You know, I'm actually
not familiar
흔한 음악은 아니라고 생각하는데
with your Uncle Max's
klezmer band.
아무튼 고마워요
So, thank you anyway.
뭐하는 거야?
What was that about?
엘리와 어썸이 결혼할때 부를
I'm helping Ellie
and awesome find a band
밴드를 정하는걸 돕고 있어
for their wedding.
그렇다면, 선생님
오늘 운이 좋으시군요
Then this, sir,
is your lucky day.
우리가 처리 할수 있겠네요
We'll handle it from here.
내가 밴드 찾는걸 돕게?
You're going
to help me find a band?
아니, 아니, 아니, 아니,
오해 했구나
Oh, no, no, no, no,
you misunderstand.
넌 벌써 밴드를 찾았어
우리야
You've found your
band. It is we.
우리가 네 누이의
결혼식때 연주해 줄 수 있어
We'll play your
sister's big day.
어, 잠깐 잠깐만
Um, wait. Wait a minute.
너희 밴드가 있어?
You guys have a band?
제프
Jeff.
레스터
Lester...
-제프스터
Jeffster!
- Jeffster!
잘 어울리는 이름이네
That seems very fitting.
사실 우리는 제스터라고
이름을 지으려 했는데
Originally, we were going to go
with the name Jester,
사람들이 우리 이름을 듣고
but we didn't want people
한 쌍의 바보를 떠올릴까봐 바꿨어
To associate us
with a couple of fools.
확실히 그렇게는 안들리네
Obviously not.
그래, 지난 밤에 뭐했어?
So, what'd you do last night?
나갔지
Went out.
음흠~
Mm-hmm.
어디 갔어?
Where'd you go?
제발, 나 지금 손님이랑 있자나
Please. I'm with a customer.
그럼, 혼자 갔어?
I mean, did you go by yourself?
저....
Um...
그래 우리 누나가
Yeah, my sister--
더 일반적인걸 좋아하거든
Her taste runs
a little more classic.
그렇지만, 우리
음악을 들어본적 없자나
But you haven't heard us.
찰스 난 니가 우리를
Charles, I'd hate to think
편견을 갖고 보는거 같아
마음이 아프다
you'd prejudge us.
음악적으로 열린마음을 가져
Don't be a musical bigot.
음
Um,
미안해 하지만 대답은 안돼야
I'm sorry, but the answer's no.
그냥 안돼
아깝지만 안될거 같아 미안해
It just is no.
It's a flat-out no. I'm sorry.
나 다른 사람 만나고 있어
괜찮지 모건?
I'm seeing someone,
okay, Morgan?
요런, 요런, 요런
Well, well, well.
진실의 때가 왔군
The truth comes out.
새 남자라...아님
내가 착각하고 있는건가?
A new man, or...
or am I assuming something here?
그니깐, 확실히 남자 맞지?
I mean, it is a man, right?
왜냐면, 넌 전에
다른 많은 경험을 해왔자나
Because we all know about
your very, very colorful past.
제발, 철 좀들어 모건
God, grow up, Morgan.
아, 쫌
Oh, please.
이봐, 이봐, 친구
Hey. Hey, buddy.
저기 냉장고 있는데에 손님이 있는데 말야
There are some customers
over in refrigerators
도움이 필요할거 같아
that might need some helping.
이따 한 두 시간 뒤에 가볼게
All right, I clocked out
a couple hours ago,
지금은 내 시간에 집중해야 겠어
so I'm on my own time here.
그정도면 됐어, 친구
Enough... buddy.
가보는게 좋을거 같아
You should probably go.
뭐 그러지, 그럼
All right, well,
너랑 네 새 남자친구 둘다
I-I hope you
and your new boyfriend
불행해졌으면 좋겠구나
are very unhappy together.
모건때문에 미안해
I'm sorry about Morgan.
넌 평생을 모건 뒤처리만 하면서
살았자나
You've spent your whole
life apologizing for him.
모르겠어?
Don't you get it?
그는 절대 철들지 않을거야
He's never going
to grow up.
내가 그를 좋아하는 백만가지 이유중에
There's a million reasons
to love him,
성숙함은 유감스럽게도 빠져있지
but unfortunately
maturity is not on that list.
그래서, 내가, 내가 듣기론
So I hear-- I heard
네게 새 남자친구가 생겼다던데
that you have a new guy,
new boyfriend...
아님 말고
or whatever.
제이슨은 멋져
Jason's great,
거기다 타코벨에서 음식을 받을때
plus an evening out doesn't
involve me on his handlebars
핸들을 잡아주지 않아도 돼
and the Taco Bell drive-thru.
무슨말인지 나도 알지
Know what you mean.
나도 몇 년 동안이나
핸들을 잡아주었는걸
I've been riding
on those handlebars for years.
저기, 그럼 우리 언제
Hey, how would you like to go
더블 데이트 같은거나 할까?
on a double date or
something sometime?
정말?
Really?
그래
Yeah.
제이슨이 오늘 자기 전시장에서
파티가 있는데
Jason's having a party
tonight at his showroom.
샴페인 보다 비싼거라고는
I mean, only thing
more expensive
자동차 밖에 없겠지만서도
than the champagne
will be the cars.
너랑 사라가 들르면 되겠다
You and Sarah should stop by.
잘 됐네
Sounds great.
네 새 남자친구
만난다니 설레이는걸
Yeah, can't wait to meet
your new boyfriend.
좋아
Okay.
와우
Wow.
잘했어
Good job.
당신이 미워요
I hate you.
내가 그녀의 새 남자친구를
만난다니 믿을수 없어요
I can't believe I have
to meet her new boyfriend.
척과 전 커플로 위장해서
Chuck and I will enter
as our cover couple,
왕에게 접근할 거에요
get close to Wang...
이 못난이 컴퓨터가
보고 잘 떠올리기만 하면 되는군
see if the skin-covered robot
flashes on anything...
그 컴퓨터가 절 말하는가 보죠?
그것 참 친절하네요
What, is that supposed
to be me? That's real nice.
왕과 삼합회와의 관련성을 밝혀내봐
Figure out any connection
Wang has to the Triad...
여기 이 GLG-20(도청기)를 이용해서말이죠
try to plant this GLG-20.
난 밴에서 네가 뭘하고 있는지
살펴볼거야
I'll be in the van monitoring
your activity.
준비됐어?
가자
All set?
Let's go.
사실 저기요
제가 생각해 봤는데요
Actually, you know what?
I-I've been thinking.
관둬
Stop that.
이번 임무가 모건을 배신하는 거라면
If our mission
is to betray Morgan,
안나에게 그가 없다는 걸 그리워
한다는걸 깨우쳐주는
I think we should have
a second mission:
두번째 임무가 필요할 거 같아요
To convince Anna of what
she's missing without him.
한가지 임무뿐이야, 멍청아
Only one mission here, moron.
오, 멍청이라구요, 그거 정말
Oh, "moron," that's...
있죠, 몽둥이랑 돌로
내 뼈를 부러뜨릴수 있지만...
You know, sticks and stones
may break my bones...
내가 테스트해보길 원하나
바토스키?
Do you want me to test
that theory, Bartowski?
-그런건 아니죠
-그렇지
Not particularly.
- No.
하~
Ha.
저기, 안나 이 행사는 뭣 땜에 하는거야?
So, uh, Anna, w-what's
the occasion for all this?
자동차 전시때문에 하는거야
It's a car preview
제이슨이 내일 열 경매에서
for an auction Jason's
having tomorrow--
쓸 자동차를 보여주는
개방 파티 같은거야
sort of an open house for cars.
그렇군
Oh.
안나, 여기 자동차들은
거의 집 값이랑 맞먹겠는데
Anna, these, these cars are
almost the price of a house.
네 남자친구는 꽤 잘사나봐
Your boyfriend must be
very successful.
비록 남자의 성공을 재기 위한
Although the,
the true measure
척도가 단지 돈이 아니라
of a man's success
사랑을 할 수 있는
is not in dollars but rather
능력에 달려 있어도 말이지
his ability to love,
그게 사실이라면
모건은 꽤나 부자인 셈이지
and if that's true,
Morgan is stinking rich.
그니까, 내 말이 맞죠 사라?
I mean, wouldn't
you agree, Sarah?
나도 너희 둘이
함께있던 모습이 그리워
I do miss you guys together.
-그래?
-응 정말
You do?
- I'm sure
제이슨은 정말 멋진 사람이지만
난 항상 너랑 모건이
Jason's a great guy,
but I'll always think
완벽한 커플이라고 생각했거든
of you and Morgan
as the perfect couple.
항상 그랬지
And she'd say
it all the time,
"귀여운 커플이 나타났다!
저기 모건이랑 안나가 와."
"cute couple alert: Here
comes Morgan and Anna."
수염난 멍청이를 광고하는건 관둬
Cut the infomercial
on the bearded loser.
왕이 나타났어
Wang just walked in.
허
Huh.
그거 이상하다
That is so strange.
뭐, 뭐가 이상해?
이거? 내가 귀를 만지는 거?
What-what's strange? That
I was touching my ear?
아니...이...이건
그냥 습진때문이야
That's-- no,
that's eczema,
절대 이상한게 아니지
Which is totally normal,
not strange.
사람들이 앓고 있는 병이니깐
People have it.
No,
아니, 사라조차 모건이랑 날
Strange Sarah even thought
커플로 생각했었다니
about Morgan and I
as a couple.
솔직히 말해서
To be honest,
넌 내가 존재하는 것도
모르고 있는줄 알았어
I didn't think you ever
really noticed me much.
그렇지 않아 안나
That's not true, Anna.
난 항상 너와 친구가 되고 싶었어
I have always thought of you
as a friend.
자기야
Honey,
이리 좀 와볼래요?
Can you come here?
제이슨, 여긴 사라랑 척이에요
Jason, this is Sarah and Chuck.
제 친구들이죠
They're my friends.
-안나의 어떤 친구들이라도
-안녕하세요
Well, any friend of Anna's...
- Hi.
이게 저희 첫만남인데도
Even though this is our,
our first time meeting,
왠지 모르게 당신에 대해
I feel as though I know
사소한 일도 알고 있다는 느낌이 드네요
every teeny, tiny,
little thing about you.
괜찮길 바래요
All good, I hope.
안녕하신가, 이놈의 시키
Hello, douche bag.
좋아, 좋아
Okay, okay.
뭐가 있지?
What do we got here?
이럴순 없어
No, it can't be.
이런 배신자(Judas;유다)
Judas.
너드허드 입니다
Nerd herd desk.
무슨일인지 알려 주시겠습니까?
Download me
on your computer emergency.
안녕하세요, 아. 저기
Hi, hi, uh,
엘리 바토스키 인데요
this is Ellie Bartowski.
제 동생이 거기 있나요?
데본이랑 제가 손님 명단을 작성하는데
Is my brother around?
Devon and I were
컴퓨터가 갑자기
in the middle of our guest
list and the computer...
멈췄어요
froze.
어, 저기 엘리,
Uh, hey, Ellie, uh,
척은 지금 다른 업무중에 있는거 같던데요
I think Chuck is out
on an install right now.
제가 전해드릴게요
I'll leave him a message.
끊어요
Okay.
저희가 지금 가서 고쳐드릴게요
Uh, we'll be right over
to fix it.
아, 고마워요 고마워요
정말 잘 됐네요
Oh, thank you,
thank you, that's great.
마침내 동생이 평범한
직장에서 일한 보람을 얻는구나
Wow, it finally pays to have
a brother in mediocre places.
음. 제퍼슨?
Um, Jefferson?
친구, 넌 거의 완벽한 기회를
날려먹을뻔 했어
Dude, you almost blew
our big chance.
우린 거기에서
오디션을 볼 수 있다구
We're going over there
to audition.
무슨 말이야?
What do you mean?
지금 당장?
Like, right now?
(에미넴-lose yourself 가사)
이봐 친구
Come on, man.
이봐, 만약 너에게 네가 원했던
If you had one shot,
one opportunity
모든것을 얻을 수 있는
to seize everything
you ever wanted,
한번의 기회가 주어진다면
잡을텐가?
one moment,
그대로 놔줄 것인가?
would you capture it
or just let it slip?
제프스터여 영원하라!
Jeffster! Lives, man.
좋아
Yes.
멋져, 환상적이야
Great, fantastic.
방금 떠오른게 있어요
I just flashed.
저 여자 이름은 스무스 라우
그리고 다들 삼합회에요
Her name is Smooth Lau,
and they're
알았어요
all Triad.
- Okay,
따라 붙어보지요
let's follow them.
저기, 음
Hey, um,
잠깐 얘기할 수 있어?
can I talk to you?
지금 당장 친구가 필요한데
I could really use a friend
right now.
물론이지
Oh, sure.
좀 이따가 따라갈게,자기
I'll catch up in a second,
sweetie.
알았어
Okay.
기다려
Wait for me.
그래
Yeah.
고마워 척
Thanks, chuckles.
다 듣고 있어
I'm all ears.
다시 부팅시키고
이 유틸리티를 실행시키면 돼요
Rebooted it
and ran a disk utility.
이제 거의 새컴퓨터 같을거에요
It's as good
as a non-new computer can be.
아 정말 고마워
Oh, thank God.
이 여자는 대동맥 판막도 교체하지만
The woman can replace
an aortic valve,
컴퓨터 화면이 얼어붙으면
but a frozen computer screen
같이 당황하지
makes her panic.
어, 저기
Uh, excuse me.
왜 내 물건들을
Why are you touching
건드리고 있어?
my things?
당신을 신나게 하기 위함이죠
I'm setting up to rock you hard.
누굴 신나게 해?
Uh, rock who hard?
우리 오디션이요
Our audition.
제프스터! 당신의 인생에 있어
Jeffster! Is going to play
가장 중요한 순간
the biggest gig of your life:
당신의 결혼식을
즐겁게 해줄 덕후들이죠
your wedding day.
저 사람 술마신거야?
Is he drunk?
정말 저사람들에게
You didn't really set them up
오디션 보라고 했어? 그랬어?
to audition, did you?
물론 아니지
Of course not.
척이 보냈을거야
Chuck must have.
마이크
Sibilance.
체크
Check.
잠깐만, 지금 당신이 할일을
다른 사람에게 맡긴거야?
Wait a minute, did you outsource
your to-do list?
아니지........
No...
척이 음악을 얼마나
좋아했는지 생각나서
I know how much
Chuck loves music.
척이라면 즐겁게
할 줄 알았지
Thought it'd be fun for him.
그랬어?
# 마, 메 모 무 #
Oh, you did?
# mah, may, moe, moo #
# 마, 메 , 무 #
# mah, may, moo #
# 마, 미 #
# mah, mee #
# 마... #
# mah... #
저기, 이봐, 우리가
오늘 할일이 많아
Uh, excuse me, guys, we,
we just have a lot to do.
오 물론이죠, 진정해요
저희가 다 알아서 설치할게요
Oh. Sure, cool, cool,
sure, we're all set.
자.. 자 시작하자
L-let's, let's do this.
지금이 아니면 안돼
Now or never.
해보자
# 마 , 메, 미, 모 #
Hang on.
# mah, may, mee, moe #
# 무....무.. #
# moo... moo... #
이건 우리가 항상 원하던 기회야
This is what we've always
wanted for Jeffster!
처음에는 이런 조그마한 무대겠지만
We start at a small venue
머지 않아
like this.
더 큰 무대에 설 수 있을거야
Pretty soon, we're
playing the big time.
좋아, 그래, 저 사람들
놀라게 해보자
Yeah, sure, we're going
to blow their minds,
근데 이것들 뒤에 뭐가 따라올까?
but where does all this lead?
공연장, 박순희들, 약물
Stadiums, groupies, drugs,
음악적 견해 차, 그리고
creative differences,
and then what?
제프스터! 해체?
Jeffster! Breaks up?
이건 너와 내 문제야
That's you and me, Jeff.
그럼 내 운명은 어떻게 되는데?
어떤 호텔 직원이
And then what's my fate?
Some chambermaid finds me
방에서 혼자 자위라도 하다가
in a hotel room, having
accidentally asphyxiated
질식해 있는 날 발견하겠지
while making love to myself?
그럴 가치는 없어
It's just not worth it!
정말 예민한 아티스트거든요
He's such a tortured artist.
그렇겠지
Mm-hmm.
이봐, 난 지금 중요한 밖에
중요한 파티가 있다구
Look, I'm having a
very important party
그리고 전에는 이런식으로
일하지 않았자나
out there, and we've never
done it this way before.
그래, 그래, 그냥 열쇠나 내놔
Yeah, yeah, just give me the keys.
내 생각엔 무슨일이 벌어지는지
나도 아는게 좋을거 같은데
I think I've earned the right
to know what's going on.
콘테이너 안에 든게 뭐야
What's in the container?
당신 일이나 신경써
여긴 내가 알아서 할테니
You mind your business,
I'll mind mine.
어쨌든 돈은 받게될거야
You're getting paid
either way.
제발 떠올라라
Come on, flash.
뭐라도 떠오르라구 제길
Flash, damn it.
내가 할게
I can help.
그건 아마 ....
He's probably...
좋아
Okay.
이봐 이건 너무 위험해
Look, this is
way too risky.
이건 내가 들인 물건이라구
I'm out after this shipment.
흠, 일이 잘 풀리면
Well, if all goes well,
우리가 다신
널 보는 일이 없을거야
we won't need another.
그리고, 뭘 그렇게 걱정하고 있어?
And what are you worried about?
국세청은 절대 이 롤스로이스를
의심하지 않을거야
Customs didn't suspect a thing
with that Rolls Royce
그게 폭발한다고 해도 말야
in the crate.
이녀석 어디갔어?
Where the hell is he?
문이 끼인거 같아
The door is jammed.
쇠지레를 가져올게
I'll go get a crowbar.
이봐, 잠깐
Hey, wait.
조용히 해봐
내가 뭘 들은거 같아
Be quiet,
I thought I heard something.
제길! 바토스키
Damn it, Bartowski.
이거 들었어?
Did you hear that?
난 제이슨이 맘에 들어 그리고
I like Jason and,
you know, on paper,
제이슨은 모건이랑 같은 점도
하나도 없고 말야
그래서 맘에 들어
he's everything Morgan's not,
so that's good.
아니, 아니 그건 나쁜거야
No, no, that's bad.
어째서?
Why?
지금 이 남자랑 모건을
계속 비교하고 있잖아
Because Morgan's the guy
you keep comparing him to.
사라 네말이 맞아
Sarah, you're totally right.
이런 세상에
Oh, my God.
내가 아직도 그를 사랑하는거 같니?
Do you think
that means I still love him?
모두 집중하라
허가 받지 않은 자가 침입했다
Attention, security, we found
an intruder on the premises.
척
Chuck.
반복한다 허가받지
않은 자가 침입했다
Repeat, we found an intruder
on the premises.
오, 안돼
Oh, no.
케이시
Casey.
이봐 잠깐
Hey, wait.
척이 발각된게 아니라면 그럼 누가
If Chuck hasn't been
captured, then...
삼합회를 염탐하고 있었다는거죠?
who is the spy
being held by Triad?
아우!
Ow!
잠, 잠, 잠 잠깐만요
W-w-w-w-wait, wait, wait.
제가 설명할게요
Let me explain!
이봐요, 제 자전거가 고장난다구요
Hey, you're going to
damage my Schwinn.
오 세상에 모건이야
모건이 잡힌거야!
Oh, my God, that's Morgan.
They've got Morgan!
이봐, 워!
Hey, whoa!
뭐요? 가서 도와줘야죠
What?
We've got to help him.
안되요 척, 그냥 이렇게
나가서 무기를 꺼냈다가는
No, Chuck, we cannot just
start pulling out weapons.
우리 위장이 드러날 거에요
We're going to blow our cover.
좋아요, 그럼
다른 작전은 뭐죠?
Okay, fine,
then what's the next option?
넌 내가 지금 이렇게
가만히 있는게 괜찮을거 같아?
You think it's easy
for me to do nothing?
나도 이렇게 속수무책으로
가만히 있는건 정말 질색이야
It goes against everything I
believe in to leave a man behind.
그럼 가만히 있지말고
뭐라도 좀 해봐요
Then don't do nothing.
Do something.
그냥 여기서 가만히
내 제일 친한 친구가
We can't just stand here
while my best friend gets
고문당하거나 살해당하는걸
보고만 있을수는 없어요
tortured or killed.
좋아요, 당신들이
아무것도 하지 않겠다면,
Fine, if you're not going
to save him...
-제가 하지요
-이봐
then I will.
- Hey.
잠, 잠깐만요
Wai-wait.
누구냐?
Who are you?
그냥 전
Nobody.
전...전...
I'm... I'm...
제 이름 말라민 스톤하트이구요
My name is, uh,
Marlamin Stoneheart.
레벨 60짜리 고블린전사지요
I'm a 60th-level
gnome warrior.
사실대로 말해
The truth.
알았어요, 알았어
Okay, okay, wow.
레벨 59에요, 그치만
이제 얼마 남지 않았다구요
59th level, you know, but
I'm-I'm, like, this close.
이 녀석이 우릴 염탐했어
I found him spying on us.
왜 그랬는지 말하는데 1초를 주지
You've got one second
to tell me why.
하나!
One!
잠, 잠, 잠, 잠,
잠깐만요
W-w-w-w-wait!
-잠깐만요,그는 첩보요원이 아니에요
-넌 대체 누구냐?
Wait, he's not a spy!
And who the hell are you?
-잠깐 무슨일이에요?
-모건?
Wait, what's going on?
- Morgan?
바이모어에서 일한다는 전 남자친구?
This is your ex from buy more?
여기서 뭐하는거야?
What are you doing here?
네 목을 부러뜨리기 전에 말해
Tell me before I break
your neck.
안돼요, 안돼
그러고 싶지 않을거에요
No, no, no, no, don't...
You don't want to do that,
난 그가 왜 여기있는지 알고 있거든요
Because I know why he's here.
그는 여기에
He's here...
척, 제발
Chuck, man...
그는 널 스토킹하기 위해 있는거야
He's here because
he's stalking you.
뭐?
What?
맞아, 사실이야
That's right, that's right.
그는 첩보요원이 아니야, 알겠어?
He's not a spy, okay?
그냥 스토커야
He's a stalker,
그 둘의 차이는
which is a thin, but-but very,
엄청 다르지
very key difference,
내 생각에는
in my opinion.
안나가 널 왜 차버렸는지 알거 같아
I see why Anna dumped you.
이 녀석은 너무 심하게
This guy is a
profoundly disturbed
상처 입어 버렸어, 알겠어?
individual, okay?
얘는 그냥....
얘는 널 떠나보내기 싫었던거야
He just can't...
He can't let go of her.
완전 사로잡히게 된거지
He's an obsessed
아직 덜 치료된 ....
but totally unthreatening...
장애인 같은거야
...sicko.
철 좀 들어 모건 그라임스
Grow up, Morgan Grimes.
병신 장애인녀석
Sicko freak.
놔줘
Let him go.
가자
Let's go.
그래도, 제일 친한
친구의 목숨은 살렸네요
Well, you just saved
your best friend's life.
그의 명예를 대가로 말이죠
At the expense of his dignity.
그래도 아직 숨은 쉬자나요
Well, at least he's still breathing.
가요
Come on.
제가 지금 찾은걸 보세요 보스
Look what I just found, boss.
이 조그만 병신놈이
Guess that little freak
그냥 스토커가 아니었군
wasn't just a stalker after all.
처리해
Kill him.
이봐
Hey.
이봐, 친구 도와줄까?
Hey, buddy, you...
You need some help?
아니
Nope.
내가 배운게 있다면 말야
I got to learn to do things
지금 부터라도 내 일은
내가 처리해야 한다는거야
on my own from now on.
이봐 모건
내가 네 기분을 상하게 했다는거 알아
Look, Morgan,
I know that I hurt
하지만, 널 보호하려고 한거야
your feelings, but I was only
trying to protect you.
우리가 꽤 오랫동안 친구였지,그치?
We've been friends for
a long time, right?
거의 기억하기도 힘들지, 친구
As long as I can remember,
buddy.
추억을 간직해
Enjoy the memories.
뭐?
What?
이봐
Buddy.
누나와 어썸이 제프스터에 대해
You got any idea what
Ellie and awesome
어떻게 생각하는지 알고 있어?
thought about Jeffster!?
그니깐, 우...우리가 완전히
연주하지는 않았지만
I mean, we... we didn't
네가 좀 좋게 말해준다면....
fully play out, but if you could
put in a good word.
제프 지금 니가 니 입으로
Jeff, I don't understand
anything
무슨 말 하는지 도통 못 알아 듣겠어
That just came out
of your mouth.
사실, 관심 없어
The truth is,
I don't care.
네 생각에 난 그냥 주말 날씨나
I know that you think
my concerns
신경쓰거나 새로들어온
are no bigger
than the weekend weather
자판기에 무슨
과자가 있나만 신경쓰겠지만
or whatever's new
in the snack machine,
사실 나도 지금 고민거리로
but I have the weight
of the damn world
머리가 터져버릴것 같거든
그러니까 괜찮다면
on my shoulders,
so if you don't mind,
네 일은 니가 해결하도록 해
figure out your own crap.
아, 마침 잘 왔어요
Good, you're here.
당신이 여기 관세서류를 보고
I need you to cross-check
당신이 어제 본 화물의
these Customs docs
with the bill of lading
서류가 있는지 확인해 주세요
that you saw
on the container yesterday.
어쩌면 그냥 거기 서서 저한테
How could you just stand there
and make me choose
모건의 생명과 우정을
놓고 고르라고 할 수 있죠?
between Morgan's life
and his friendship?
안나가 먼저 그가
누구인지를 말하지 않았으니깐요
That wasn't going to happen
because Anna vouched for him.
그가 저에게 어떤 의미인지 모르는 군요
You don't get who he is to me.
아뇨, 잘 알아요
No, I get it.
당신과 제일 친한 친구자나요
He's your best friend.
저기, 당신이 그렇게 말했어도
You know, you say that,
난 당신이 제대로 알지 못하는거 같아요
but I don't think you
have a clue what it means.
저기, 사라....
Look, Sarah...
전 부모님이 안계셔요
I don't have parents.
사실 그렇지는 않죠
I mean, not really.
당신이 절 불쌍하게
여길까봐 여지껏
And I don't talk
말하지 않고
about it because
that's just the way
참아왔던거죠
that things are now.
그래도 항상 그렇지는 않았어요
But it wasn't always this way.
모건은 우리 엄마가 돌아가시던날 함께 해줬어요
Morgan was there the first day
that my mom took off.
머 위로라고 해주진 않았어요, 사실
He didn't say much
because, honestly,
5학년짜리가
그 상황에서 뭐라고 하겠어요
what is a fifth grader
supposed to say?
그래도 우린 앉아서 치즈케揚 나눠먹고
But we sat there and split
a cherry cheesecake
밤새 '젤다의 전설'을 했죠
and played Legend of Zelda
all night long.
그리고, 우리 아버지....
그건 좀 다른 이야기이지만
And my dad...
Well, that's a whole...
그래도 모건은 그때도
내 곁에 있어줬어요
other story, but Morgan
was there for that, too.
모건은 제게 그냥
친한 친구 이상의 의미에요
Morgan is more
than just my best friend.
그는 제 가족이에요
He's my family.
당신이 여기오기 전에
Before you got here
당신이 떠나고 난뒤에도
모건은 제 가족이고, 또 그럴거에요
and long after you've gone,
Morgan is my family.
우리가 어제 삼합회의 화물에
Last night, we failed to learn
내용물을 확인하는걸 실패했지요
the contents of the
Triad's container,
그리고 우리는 그 안에
and now we don't know
이 도시에 나돌
어떤 무기나 약물이 들어서
what kind of drugs or weapons
are floating around in the city.
당신이 모건과의 우정을
감사히 여기고
And while I appreciate
your friendship with Morgan,
화물에 집중하지 않는 동안
losing sight of that container
다른 많은 사람들의 친구를
위험에 빠뜨릴지를 알아야 해요
endangers many people's
best friends.
당신 친구만이 아니라요
Not just yours, Chuck.
이봐 지금은 안돼
Not a good time, bro.
친구, 문틈에는 발을 넣었어야지
Dude, you're supposed to
stop a door with your foot.
이루어진적 없는 꿈을
Have you ever had a dream
그려 본적 있어?
that's never come true?
흠...
Hmm.
아니
No.
좋아
Okay.
절대 이루어 지지 않을 꿈을
Have you ever had a best friend
꾸고 있는 친구를 본 적 있어?
with a dream
that's never come true?
레스터가 어제
노래하길 두려워했지만
Lester was scared
to sing yesterday,
그 녀석은 천사도 울게만들
but he has a voice
목소리를 갖고 있어
that makes angels cry.
제발, 제프스터에게
한번만 더 기회를 줘
Please, give Jeffster
another chance.
제프 넌 이상한 녀석이야
Jeff, you're a weird dude,
그렇지만, 아무리 이상한 녀석이라도
but I guess even
a weird dude
친구가 있을 수 있다고 생각해
like you can have a friend.
어떻게 엘리를
설득시킬지는 모르겠지만
I don't know how I'm
gonna convince Ellie,
오디션을 준비해야 할거야
but you got yourself
another audition.
내가 가서 말해볼까?
You want me to talk to her?
우린 만난적이 있잖아
We have a rapport.
이봐, 모건 제발 제발
Hey, Morgan,
will you please, please
나랑 잠시만 이야기 해줄래?
just talk to me
for one second?
너랑 얘기할 거리 없어
I have nothing left
to say to you, dude.
네가 너와 다신 말하지 않기 전에
One question, though,
한가지 질문이 있어
before, uh, I never
speak to you again.
어떻게 날 배신한게 날 구한게 된거지?
How did you betraying me
turn into you saving me?
널 배신해서 미안해
I'm sorry for betraying you.
아냐, 임마 미안하다고 할 필요없어
No, dude, you don't
get to say sorry.
니말이 맞아, 미안하다는
말로는 충분하지 않지
You're right,
sorry isn't good enough.
그건 싸구려 밴드를..
It's a cheap band-aid...
관둬 짜샤,
난 이해 못해
Stop it, dude,
you don't get it.
이건 다 내 탓이야
This whole thing is my fault.
내 탓이라구
Man, it's me.
내가 다 자초한 일이야
I made this mess.
니가 나보고 염탐질하지 말라고 경고했자나
You warned me not to spy.
하지만, 난 가서 또 하고 있었지
I went and did it anyway.
너도 알다시피 난 거기서
또 머저리짓 하고 있었고
You know, I'm so sick
of you being right
니가 날 또 구해 줬지
and then having to bail me out.
너도 날 많이 구해줬자나
You've bailed me out
plenty of times.
난 내 삶을 정상적으로 바꾸는데
또 네 도움을 받을 수는 없어
I can't count on you
to fix things my whole life.
-물론 그럴수 있지
-이봐
Of course you can.
- Look,
이제는 내가 저지른
실수들의 대가를 받고
It's time for me to pay
for my own mistakes,
나 스스로 싸워야 할때야
fight my own battles.
저기, 친구 나....
Um, buddy, I...
난 다른 싸움이 이제 막 시작 된거 같아
I would maybe start
with a different battle.
이봐, 고개 숙이고, 조용히 있으면
Look, just keep it down,
remain calm,
곧 끝날거야
and this will all be over soon.
아냐, 임마 이게 뭔지 알아?
No, dude, you know
what this is?
이건 니가 날 또 구하는 거야
This is just you
saving me again, man.
아냐, 그렇지 않아
No, no, it's not.
최악의 상황으로부터,
친한 두 친구가 피해있는거야
This is two best friends hiding
from a terrible beating.
지금이 기회야
The time is now, okay?
지금이 바로 내
스스로 일어설 때야
Time for me to stand
up for myself.
난 지금 나가서 저 험악하고
무자비한 불량배들과 맞서
I have to go out there to
those beefy, heartless thugs
대가를 치르고 남자가 될거야
and take it like a grown man.
여자를 염탐하는 남자지 좋아
A grown man who spies
on women, fine,
하지만 이제...
but still...
이제 관둘거야 척 알겠어?
I'm done, Chuck, okay?
난 이제 더이상 니가 날 구하길 원치 않아
I won't have you
saving me anymore.
잠깐, 잠깐, 잠깐,
잠깐만
No, wait,
wait, wait, wait.
모건 모건 기다려 기다려
Morgan, Morgan,
wait, wait.
네 입에서 썩은 내가 나는데 그냥 나갈 순 없어
You can't... you can't just
go out there with your..
지금 농담하냐?
with your breath stinking like garbage.
- Are you kidding me?
지금 저녀석들이 날 패러 왔는데
Way to kick a man
when he's about to be beat down.
내 수염에 비듬이 있나 없나
신경써 줘야 하는거야?
I'm short and occasionally
have dandruff in my beard.
이 녀석들이 내
수염이라도 뜯어갈까봐 그래?
Do you want to riff
on me for that, too?
아니 난 그냥....
No, I... I wouldn't...
너 수염에 비듬있어?
You have dandruff in your beard?
난 그냥...아니다.... 내말은
I would... No,
all I'm saying is that
그래도, 깨끗이 하고 가야지
maybe you should freshen up
first, you know.
왜 잠자는 사자의 코털을 당기려 해?
Why... why poke an already
pissed off bear?
허?
Huh?
그래
Ah-ah.
좋아 그럼
All right, just...
이거 향이 세다
이게 뭐야? 민트햐.
That's strong--
what is that, pep...
민트향인가?
is that just peppermint?
진짜 빠르네
That's quick.
이봐
Hey.
어젯밤 왔던 스토커 녀석 못봤어?
You seen that stalker from
the party the other night?
예, 저기 뒤로 가는거 봤어요
Yeah, yeah, I think
he actually went out the back.
어......
Uh...
뭘 썰고 자르고 하는 거 같고
Talking about getting a slice
or something
떠드는 것 같았는데
like that, so...
살살하세요
Take it easy.
무슨 일이에요
Hey, what is it?
-척이 호출했어
-가요
Chuck's in trouble.
Let's go.
난 오늘 휴일이었는데
So much for my day off.
척, 와서 이것 좀 봐봐
Chuck, I want you
to see something.
그럴 시간 없어 지금 난
No time-- I'm actually
right in the middle
이 귀찮은 기구를 치우는 중이라
of moving this very cumbersome
and time-sensitive appliance,
-그래서 안나, 안나, 안나
-어서
so I... Anna, Anna, Anna.
- Come on.
잠깐이면 돼
It'll just take a second.
봐바 내 남자친구가 티비에 나와
Look, my boyfriend's on TV.
LA시내에서 안토니오 루이즈 입니다
Antonio Ruiz reporting
from downtown Los Angeles
제 옆에는 기업가인
제이슨 왕이 있는데요
Where I'm standing
with entrepreneur, Jason Wang.
오늘 매우 특별한 자동차들로
On the auction block today,
a collection
경매를 여신다고 하는데
of very fine automobiles...
유명인사들이 한자리에 모여
Celebrities and dignitaries
are everywhere
차에 대한 열정을
with one thing in common.
보여 주고 있습니다
...a passion for cars.
이런 세상에 경매야
Oh, my God, the auction.
난 낄수 없어
Don't rub it in.
난 일해야 하니깐
I have to work.
척, 뭐에요?
Chuck, what is it?
그냥 경매에 관해서 떠오른게 있어요
I just flashed-- we have
to get to the auction.
삼합회는 중국 대사를
죽이려 할거에요
Triads are gonna kill
the Chinese Ambassador.
왜 대사가 삼합회가
있는 곳까지 걸어가겠어요?
Why would he walk
into a known Triad den?
왕은 합법적으로 일하는 모양이지
Wang's got
a legitimate business.
왕이 삼합회라는 걸 대사는 모르고 있고
The Ambassador doesn't know
Wang's Triad.
그곳은 대사에게는 안전한 곳이 아니겠군요
Which is exactly why it's not
a very safe place for him.
이봐요, 어서 모건을 데리고....
Look, we just got
to get Morgan...
잠깐
Wait.
모건!
Morgan!
-차에 있어요
-차에 있어
Stay in the car, Chuck.
내가 어떻게 모건을 그냥
What... How can I stay
in the car when I have
-그렇게 두고 차에만 있을수 있어요 -제발요 명령에 따라줘요
to go save Morgan?
- Please, Chuck, just follow orders.
바토스키 너 꼭 포스터에 나오는
불장난 하는 애들로 같아
Bartowski, you're like the
poster child for friendly fire.
이런 세상에
Oh, my God.
이런 세상에 폭탄이야
Oh, my God, it's a bomb.
대사님
Ambassador...
새 차량을 구입하신걸 축하드립니다
congratulations
on your new rolls.
아, 감사해요
Oh, thank you.
꼭 한대 갖길 원했는데 잘됐군요
It's always been my
dream to own one.
어젯밤의 문제거리는 다 처리했어?
You take care
of last night's problem?
죽었어?
He dead?
아직
Not yet.
어떻게 처리 할까요?
What do you want us
to do with him?
좋은 생각이 있어
I got a great idea.
대사의 차를 얻어타고 가는거지
He can hitch a ride
with the Ambassador.
오 이런
Oh, God.
이게 바로 일석이조지
Kill two birds with one bomb.
저기요 들어봐요
Hey, listen, listen.
삼합회가 폭탄을 롤스로이스에 달아놨어요
Triads implanted a bomb
in the Rolls Royce,
그리고 모건을 트렁크에 넣어놨구요
and they put Morgan
in the trunk.
어서 멈춰야 해요
We've got to stop it.
척 지금 있는데서 꼼작말고 기다려요
Chuck, stay right
where you are.
내가 차를 맡을게요
당신이 척을 맡아요
I'll get the car,
you get Chuck.
케이시 화물칸은 비어있어요
Casey, the container is empty,
차는 급하게 치운 모양이에요
and the car has already been
dispatched.
케이시 내 말 들려요?
Casey, do you copy?
케이시, 들리냐구요!
Casey, do you copy?!
너처럼 예쁜 계집이 경찰이라니, 와우
Pretty girl like you
is a cop-- whew.
그 얼굴을 망치려니 미안한걸
Shame I gotta mess up that face.
잠깐, 잠깐, 잠깐
멈춰요 멈춰
Wait, wait, wait!
Stop! Stop!
멈춰요 당신차에
폭탄이 설치되어 있어요
Stop, there's a
bomb in your car!
삼합회의 함정이야, 운전해!
It's a Triad trap, move!
안돼! 안돼요
No! No...
제발 말 좀 들어라
바토스키
Learn to follow an order,
Bartowski!
이봐.....아!
Hey... Aah!
-문 좀 열어 -안 돼요!
Let me in!
- I can't!
내가 열어주면 모건을
못 구하게 할거잖아요
If I do that, you're not going
to let me save Morgan.
완전 바보는 아니구만
Proving you're
not a complete idiot.
- 문열어!
- 안돼요!
Let me in!
- Nope! No!
모건은 제 제일친한 친구에요,알아요?
He's my best friend, Casey,
all right?!
당신이 말했듯이 누구도
버리고 갈 수 없다구요
It's like you said,
leave no man behind!
무슨 말인지 알겠어
Okay, tell you what.
날 들여보내 주면 그 수염난 멍청이를
구하는걸 돕는다고 약속하지
If you let me in, I promise to
help you save the bearded loser.
-약속해요?
-약속하지
You promise?
- I promise.
-충성?(Semper Fi?)
-충성할게
Semper Fi?
- Semper Fidelis.
뭐하는거에요?
Oh! What are you doing?
뭐하는거에요?!
What are you doing?!
모건을 구하는걸 돕는다고 했잖아요
You promised that you'd
help me save Morgan.
네가 운전하는걸
놔둔다고 말하진 않았지
I didn't promise
I'd let you drive.
그런걸로도 운전 할 수 있어요?
There's a remote control
for this thing?
미치겠네 세상에
This is crazy.
저 차요, 저차
안돼.....오! 오!
The Rolls, the Rolls,
don't... oh! Oh!
워!워!국토안보부 소속
존 케이시 소령입니다
Whoa, whoa! Major John Casey,
National Security Agency.
이게 제 배지입니다
This is my badge?
총 치우세요,
좋아요, 진정해요
Safety that weapon.
It's cool, relax.
대사의 목숨을
구하기 위해 왔습니다
We're here to stop an attempt
on the Ambassador's life.
진정해요
Be cool.
단지 도와주려 하는거에요
We're just trying to help.
폭탄이다!
Bomb!
엎드려!!
움직이지마!
On the ground!
Don't move!
지금 상황을 안 좋게 만들고 있어!
You're risking your life!
아뇨, 모건을 구하는 중이에요
No, I'm saving Morgan's!
바보 처럼 굴지마
Don't be an idiot.
머리 숙여!! 머리 숙이라구!
Head down!
진정해
Easy.
CIA다, 그 사람 놔줘
Hey, CIA. Let him go.
척은 어디있어요?
Where's Chuck?
폭탄과 함께
모자란 영웅노릇하러 갔어
Heroic imbecile took
off with the bomb.
이런 세상에, 척
Oh, my God, Chuck.
꽤 볼만하죠?
That was pretty sweet, huh?
뭐요?
What?
아 제가 저기 있다고....
Did you think that I was...?
그냥 전 이걸.......
No, I was just using the...
이리 내
Give me that.
미안해요
Sorry.
음
Um...
진짜 마지막 부탁인데
Last-last favor.
트렁크에서 뭐 좀 꺼내는 것 좀 도와줄래요?
Would you mind helping me get
something out of the trunk?
-오...
-오...이봐
Oh...
- Oh, yeah, hey.
이봐, 괜찮아?
Hey...
are you okay?
진짜 걱정했어
You really had me worried.
아, 이런, 너무 쪽팔린다
Oh, man...
I'm so embarrassed.
내 명예를 위해 쥐뿔도 한게 없어
I can't even get my ass
kicked with any dignity.
내가 기절했다니 말도안돼
Dude, I can't believe
I fainted.
그래...
Yeah...
그래...그래...
Yeah, yeah...
기절했지
You fainted.
완전 겁쟁이야
I'm such a coward.
잘 모르겠어 난 말야
I don't know, I guess...
싸움을 두려움을
Just the fear of a fight,
감당하기엔 너무 약한가봐
must've been too much for me.
미안 척
And I'm sorry, Chuck.
니가 날 구해야만 했다는게 미안해
I'm sorry that
you had to save me...
또 다시
Again.
이봐, 모건........
Come on. Morgan...
네가 나에게 무슨
의미인지 알기나 해?
Don't you know
who you are to me?
니가 나에게 해준 것들이
Don't you know
what you mean to me?
나에게 무슨
의미인지 알기나 해?
All that you've done?
고마워
Thank you.
신경쓰지마
You're welcome.
머리 좀 그만
쓰다듬었으면 하는데, 친구
You think you could butch it up
just a bit, though, bro.
그냥....
Just like...
스무스 라우와 일당들은 체포되었다네
Smooth Lau and her band
of cohorts were apprehended
그리고, 제이슨 왕은 보호 중에 있지
at the scene, and Jason Wang has
just been taken into custody.
아마 감옥에서 꽤 오해 있어야 할걸세
They will all be spending
a lot of time in prison
-고맙네 다들
-고맙습니다, 장관님
thanks to all of you.
- Thank you, General.
게다가 사건이후 메이 쉥 대사가
Furthermore, this incident
has left Ambassador Mei Sheng
삼합회를 무너뜨리는데
힘을 쏟고 있다네
with a renewed vigor
to crack down on Triad crime
여기서도, 바다 건너에서도
both here and overseas.
자, 그럼 난 저녁 약속에
늦은거 같아 실례하겠네
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I am late for my evening plans.
저, 장관님 실례지만, 오늘 저녁에
Uh, General, um,
if you don't mind me asking...
확실히 무슨 계획이 있는지 여쭈어 봐도 될까요?
what exactly is your version
of evening plans?
바토스키!
Bartowski!
그건 기밀이 아니라네 소령
It's not top secret, Major.
코스모에서 콘돌라자(前 미 국방장관)
와 만나기로 했다네
I'm meeting Condoleeza
for cosmos.
나도 친구가 있다네
Even I have friends.
척에게 음악 부분을 미뤄서 미안해
Sorry about delegating the music
stuff to Chuck.
하지만, 말로만 그러는게 아니라
But an apology is just words
행동으로도 보여줄게
if it's not followed up
by actions.
그래서 꽃도 사고, 케葯 준비했지
So I got the flowers,
I bought the cake,
그리고 내가 할일의 절반을 해냈어
and I took care of your half
of the to-do list.
너무 고마워, 데본
That's very sweet, Devon.
그리고 밴드를 찾는것도 노력하고 있지
I'm also back in charge
of finding the band,
그래서 우리가 여기있는거야
which is why we're here.
뭐?
What?
파트너쉽은 신뢰야 자기
Partnership is trust, babe.
이리와
Come on.
파트너쉽은 신뢰야
Partnership is trust.
할 수 없어
I can't do this, man.
할 수 있어
나도 잘 알아
You can, I know you can.
안돼, 전에 봤자나
No...
you see before,
제프 난 밴드가 해체되는게
Jeff, I wasn't really scared
두려운게 아니야
that the band was going
to break up.
사실 난 그냥 ....
The truth is,
I was just sc...
쉬, 쉬, 쉬
Shh, shh, shh.
절대 이루어지지
않을 꿈을 꾼적 있어?
You ever had a dream
that's never come true?
너 자신을 위해
I'm asking you to sing,
노래 하라는게 아니야
not for yourself...
날 위해 해줘
do it for me.
(toto - africa)
# I hear the drums echoing
tonight #
오늘밤 메아리치는 북소리가 들려
# I hear the drums echoing
tonight #
# but she hears only whispers
of some quiet conversation #
하지만 그녀에게 들리는 건
나직이 들리는 대화의 속삭임뿐이야
# but she hears only whispers
of some quiet conversation #
자기, 진짜 이 시시한 밴드를
Honey, you're not seriously
considering this lame band
우리 결혼식에 쓸건 아니지?
for our wedding day?
# kilimanjaro rises like olympus
above the serengeti #
저 높은 킬리만자로 산이나
세렝게티 위에 솟은 올림푸스 산처럼
# kilimanjaro rises like olympus
above the serengeti #
그래도 저 녀석들이 꿈을
이룰수 있게 해줄순 있자나
No. But let a man have
his dream.
비록 5분 동안이라도 말이야
Even if it is for five minutes.
# hurry, boy,
it's waiting there for you #
서둘러라, 그녀가 저기서 널 기다리잖니
# hurry, boy,
it's waiting there for you #
# gonna take a lot to drag me
away from you #
나를 당신에게서
떼어 놓기는 힘들거야
# gonna take a lot to drag me
away from you #
# there's nothing that a hundred
men or more could ever do #
백 명의 사람, 아니
더 많은 사람이라도 그렇게 할 수는 없어
# there's nothing that a hundred
men or more could ever do #
# I bless the rains
down in Africa #
아프리카에 내리는 비를 축복하며
# I bless the rains
down in Africa #
# gonna take some time to do
the things we never had... #
우리가 경험하지 못했던
일을 하며 시간을 보낼거야
# gonna take some time to do
the things we never had... #
내가 사과할게요
I wanted to apologize.
당신과 모건과의 우정 문제때문에
I could've been
more sensitive before
조금은 감정적이 된 것 같아요
about your friendship
with Morgan.
그냥, 전 그냥
It's just,
it's difficult,
내 인생에서 날 그렇게 걱정해주는
I don't really have anyone
in my life like that, who...
사람이 없었거든요
who cares about me.
# gonna take a lot to drag me #
나를 당신에게서
# away from you #
떼어 놓기는 힘들거야
-아뇨 있어요
Yeah, you do.
# away from you #
# there's nothing that a hundred
men or more could ever do #
백 명의 사람, 아니 더 많은
사람이라도 그렇게 할 수는 없어
# there's nothing that a hundred
men or more could ever do #
# I bless the rains
down in Africa... #
아프리카에 내리는 비를 축복하며
# I bless the rains
down in Africa... #
안나
Anna...
저기, 이 말을 훨씬 더 오래 전에 했어야 했어
Listen, I-I should've said this
to you a long time ago.
괜찮지?
All right?
음....안나 우...
Um, but, Anna Wu...
당신을 사...사...사..아니
I lo...
많이 좋아 합니다
I like you...
very, very much.
# it's gonna take a lot
to drag me away from you #
나를 당신에게서
떼어 놓기는 힘들거야
# it's gonna take a lot
to drag me away from you #
# there's nothing that a hundred
men or more could ever do #
백 명의 사람, 아니 더 많은
사람이라도 그렇게 할 수는 없어
# there's nothing that a hundred
men or more could ever do #
# I bless the rains
down in Africa... #
아프리카에 내리는 비를 축복하며
# I bless the rains
down in Africa... #
이봐
Hey, guys.
우릴 봐바
Look at us, man--
둘 다 여자친구가 있어
We both got girlfriends.
# I bless the rains
down in Africa #
아프리카에 내리는 비를 축복하며
# I bless the rains
down in Africa #
너만큼 나도 기분 좋아,짜샤
It's as good as it gets, man.
# I bless the rain #
아프리카에 내리는 비를 축복하며
# I bless the rains
down in Africa #
아프리카에 내리는 비를 축복하며
# I bless the rains
down in Africa #
# I bless the rain #
아프리카에 내리는 비를 축복하며
# I bless the rains
down in Africa... #
아프리카에 내리는 비를 축복하며
# I bless the rains
down in Africa... #
Subtitles by LeapinLar